Resume

Masuku Arnold

E-mail: arnold.masukux@gmail.com

Mobile: +256707870227

Personal Career objectives

To obtain a fresher position as a software engineer in a fast-paced organization where technical skills and creative thinking are useful. A highly motivated software engineer seeking to get a position in a reputed company, where I can use my skills and knowledge to learn new things and grow as a software developer

Personal Information

Name - Arnold
Surname - Masuku
Date of Birth - 26-09-1999
I.D. Number - N8ATQ6CF
Passport Number - MA102135
Gender - Male

Marital Status - Single

Languages - English, Zulu , Ndebele, shona

Education

- IGCSE O -Level Kalibu Academy 2017
- Advanced Subsidiary Kalibu Academy 2018-19
- Python Programming Coursera 2019-20
- Full stack Engineer Code-academy 2020-21
- Software Engineering Cavendish University 2020-now
- Dozens of charity awards and NGO trainings
- Dozens of global competition participation including Hult prize, IEEE Extreme programming.

	Core skills /strengths	
 Self-motivated Listening and writing skills. Passionate, energetic and excellent with people Quick learner who is proactive and assertive Excellent time management skills. 	 Excellent planning and organizational skills. Ability to work collaboratively and complete work before deadlines Excellent team player who is flexible & very approachable 	 Dedicated Christian who has the vulnerable and elderly at heart Recommendable guiding and counseling skills.

Career Summary

Position Held	Company	Period
IEEE Computer society Ambassador. IEEE Extreme programming	IEEE(Institute Of Electrical And Electronics Engineers	Dec 2019 to date
Ambassador. IEEE MAKEFAIR Ambassador	Inc)	
Lead web designer	Celebrations Africa	Dec 2019- 2020
Lead IT personal	Jotinah The Nurture	Jun 2019 - date
IT personal	Nchenchere Eldery project	Sep 2015- 2019

References

Head of Department (Humanities)

Professor Tiffany Banda University of Witwaterstand, Johanneburg South Africa Tel +265888 351 019/ +265 996 634 584

State House Uganda

Dr Christine Mwebesea Tel +256 772477098 tmwebesa@gmail.com